murgent.com 2005-04-04

# mUrgent Privacy Policy

**Privacy Policy**

We can be reached by email at [support@murgent.com](mailto:support@murgent.com) or by phone at 714.918.3732 M-F from 8am to 5pm Pacific Standard Time. 

Your trust in our company is just as important to us as your business. If you feel we are not following the privacy policy dictated herein, please contact us via email or phone at the above address and phone number. This privacy policy applies to registered users and site visitors of [mUrgent.com](http://www.murgent.com/), [emarketing-manager.com](http://www.emarketing-manager.com/), [emarketingautomation.com](http://www.emarketingautomations.com/), affiliate sites owned by mUrgent, and EMPACT software. If you have questions regarding the practices of our paid customers, please contact that company directly. mUrgent Corporation does not condone or approve email or SMS abuse or email campaigns that are demeaning, vulgar, or otherwise offensive. To view more on mUrgent’s strict anti-spam policy, Anti-Spam Policy.

**  
Secure Login and Information Transfer for EMPACT**  
EMPACT subscribers are identified by a validated secure server certificates (SSL) through a username and password. EMPACT subscribers are paying mUrgent customers who have agreed to our Terms of Service for the purpose of deploying email and SMS campaigns to the benefit of their customers. mUrgent Corporation ensures that all usernames, passwords, contact lists, and billing information remain encrypted to both internal and external parties by SSL. mUrgent Corporation also exercises appropriate security measures where all data is physically stored to protect the personal and financial information of our customers. 

**Personal Information and Third Parties**  
Personal information submitted by visitors through [www.murgent.com](http://www.murgent.com/) is used for follow-up and discarded. Content of inquiries may also be used to improve content and usability on [www.murgent.com](http://www.murgent.com/). We reserve the right to notify the visitor that the content has been updated. Visitor information is never sold or shared with other organizations for commercial use. Visitors who supply us with their telephone numbers on-line may receive a follow-up call if sales information is requested. 

Personal information of paid EMPACT subscribers is never sold or traded with third parties without written permission of the individual or company. Paid EMPACT subscribers must understand that a transfer of billing information is necessary to set up services. Your personal information may be released only if instructed by the proper government authorities, or if additional services are requested by the subscriber from one of mUrgent’s partners. mUrgent will not share any more personal information than is necessary to set up the transaction for billing or additional services. mUrgent only does business with those companies who have agreed to this Privacy Policy. 

**Opting-Out of Contacts from[www.murgent.com](http://www.murgent.com/) and EMPACT subscribers**  
Visitors of [www.murgent.com](http://www.murgent.com/) who sign up to receive newsletters from mUrgent Corporation or other EMPACT subscribers and no longer wish to continue service may opt-out at any time through the link provided at the bottom of each email, or simply email mUrgent at [support@murgent.com](mailto:support@murgent.com).
